<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://justfunky.com/blogs/news.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://justfunky.com/blogs/news"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://justfunky.com/blogs/news.atom"/>
  <title>Just Funky LLC - Press Releases</title>
  <updated>2017-02-02T14:56:00-05:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Just Funky LLC</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://justfunky.com/blogs/news/just-funky-continues-global-expansion-with-new-o-ce-in-delhi-india</id>
    <published>2017-02-02T14:56:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2017-04-13T06:30:11-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://justfunky.com/blogs/news/just-funky-continues-global-expansion-with-new-o-ce-in-delhi-india"/>
    <title>Just Funky Continues Global Expansion with New Oﬃce in Delhi, India</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mike Gordon</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1881/5889/files/6a490e8206b670a3dfe281dcd551.jpg?v=1491936824" style="float: left;">
<p class="article-summary">Expanding from just one small oﬃce with ﬁve employees in 2012, Just Funky has grown rapidly to over 110 employees cross the globe.</p>
<div class="marbot-15 html-content">
<p><strong class="date-line">Wooster, OH, February 2, 2017 (Newswire.com) - </strong><a href="http://justfunky.com/" target="_blank">​​Just Funky</a>, a premiere manufacturer of licensed and private label merchandise for the mainstream retail market, has expanded their international presence with a new oﬃce in Delhi, India. In 2014, Just Funky’s Delhi oﬃce had 16 team members, recently expanding to 56. The new, upgraded oﬃce, a beautiful glass building in the corporate oﬃce area of Delhi, will accommodate this team expansion.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.justfunky.com/" target="_blank">Just Funky's</a> corporate oﬃce is located in Wooster, Ohio, with additional oﬃces located in Richfield, Ohio; Columbus, Ohio; Los Angeles; Hong Kong, China, and New Delhi, India. Just Funky is looking at further expansion in 2017, planning to add another 17 positions within the ﬁrst quarter of the New Year.</p>
<p>Continued expansion will be a major focus for <a href="http://justfunky.com/" target="_blank">Just Funky</a> throughout 2017, with the company hoping to start 2018 with 170 full-time team members globally.</p>
<p>“Just Funky has had tremendous growth since its inception, and we continue to expand globally adding additional staﬃng to meet the high demand,” says <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/raj-arora-87150b9/" target="_blank">Raj Arora</a>, CEO of Just Funky. “Our growth really speaks to the quality of products we produce and value we provide our customer base. Just Funky provides an unparalleled service that just isn’t matched in the marketplace.”</p>
<p>Just Funky strives to create the most innovative products. The company’s team of talented designers, trend scouts, marketing and licensing experts, and production specialists focus on analyzing trends, developing revolutionary designs and products, and translating them into actual product for mainstream retail. The company’s distribution team, in collaboration with worldwide retailers, department stores and independent sellers, ensures maximum exposure in countries around the globe for its partners.</p>
<p><a href="http://justfunky.com/" target="_blank">Just Funky</a> currently holds more than 200 A-list licenses in its portfolio including Walking Dead, Bob Marley, Aerosmith, Breaking Bad, Doctor Who and many others. The company’s products and merchandise are distributed through major retailing partners around the world including Spencer's, Hot Topics, FYE, Think Geek, , as well as through more than 15,000 independent stores and online platforms. For more information about the company and its products and partners, visit JustFunky.com.</p>
<p><strong>About Just Funky</strong></p>
<p>Founded in 2012, Just Funky is a major supplier of licensed and private label goods for the mainstream retail market. The family- owned business is led by executives with a combined 44 years of experience in creative development, manufacturing, retail, and licensing in decor and apparel, beverage ware, and impulse and novelty. For more information, visit JustFunky.com.</p>
<p><strong>Contact</strong></p>
<p>201 E. Liberty Street, Suite 202<br>Wooster, Ohio 44691<br>United States<br>234-249-0145​<br><a href="mailto:pranav@justfunky.com" target="_blank">pr@justfunky.com</a><br><a href="http://www.justfunky.com/" target="_blank">http://www.justfunky.com/</a></p>
<p>Source: Just Funky</p>
</div>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://justfunky.com/blogs/news/just-funky-starts-the-year-with-a-new-hq</id>
    <published>2017-02-02T00:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2017-04-13T07:22:34-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://justfunky.com/blogs/news/just-funky-starts-the-year-with-a-new-hq"/>
    <title>Just Funky Starts the Year with a New HQ</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mike Gordon</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p style="float: left;"><strong class="date-line"><br><a href="http://justfunky.com/" target="_blank"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1881/5889/files/justfunky_logo1_13047283-9579-4bd1-a94f-579ae1444145_large.png?v=1492000465" style="float: left;"></a>Richfield, Ohio, February 2, 2017 (Newswire.com) - </strong><a href="http://justfunky.com/" target="_blank">Just Funky</a>, a premiere manufacturer of licensed merchandise for the mainstream retail market, today announced that it is expanding its corporate headquarters from 201 E. Liberty St. Wooster, Ohio to 160 Highlander Parkway Richfield, Ohio.</p>
<p>"This move allows us to take advantage of Cleveland’s and Akron’s strong talent pool and cost-effective environment to continue building the company into a leading provider of licensed merchandised goods," said <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/raj-arora-87150b9/" target="_blank">Raj Arora</a>, CEO.</p>
<p>According to <a href="http://justfunky.com/" target="_blank">Just Funky’s</a> Head of Division, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/pranav-arora1/" target="_blank">Pranav Arora</a>, the move was necessitated by the significant growth the company has realized in the last few years. "As our products and reputation have become better known in the industry, demand has risen – and quickly," said <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/pranav-arora1/" target="_blank">Arora</a>.</p>
<p><a href="http://justfunky.com/" target="_blank">Just Funky’s</a> President, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/shivani-arora-b699166a/" target="_blank">Shivani Arora</a> commented, "Our new office space is 50 percent larger than our previous offices and offers a more efficient layout. It will support our continued growth and expansion, and provide a better work environment for current and future team members. It underscores our commitment to both our customers and our employees."</p>
<p><strong>About Just Funky</strong></p>
<p>Just Funky is a premiere manufacturer of licensed and private label merchandise for the mainstream retail market. As a family owned business, our executives have combined over 44 years of experience in manufacturing, licensing, retail and creative development in such areas as beverageware, impulse/novelty, decor, and apparel.</p>
<p>Just Funky’s main goal is to create the most innovative product with unmatched quality. We focus on analyzing trends, developing revolutionary designs and products, and translating them into actual product for mainstream retail.</p>
<p>Want to contact Just Funky?</p>
<p>pr@justfunky.com<br>234-249-0145<br>www.justfunky.com</p>
<p>Source: Just Funky</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://justfunky.com/blogs/news/latest-news-feed</id>
    <published>2017-02-01T00:00:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2017-04-13T07:20:01-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://justfunky.com/blogs/news/latest-news-feed"/>
    <title>Just Funky Announces Expansion in the European Marketplace</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mike Gordon</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1881/5889/files/blog1.jpg?v=1490904906" style="float: left;">
<p><strong class="date-line">Columbus, Ohio, February 6, 2017 (Newswire.com) - </strong><a href="http://www.just-funky.uk/" target="_blank">​​Just Funky</a>, a premier manufacturing company is growing at astronomical rate, selling to more than 20,000 independent stores across North America and now the European Union. With more than 110 employees, <a href="http://www.just-funky.com/" target="_blank">Just Funky</a> has added to their Ohio headquarters with presences in major cities across the world including Los Angeles, Hong Kong, and New Delhi.</p>
<p>After achieving unprecedented success in the United States, <a href="http://www.just-funky.uk/" target="_blank">Just Funky</a> has decided to conquer the international market. With big name retailers like Target, , Spencers Gifts, Loot Crate , and many more, Just Funky looks forward to connecting with new brands and consumers  around the world.</p>
<p>“We are very excited to be able to cater to the European audience, and give the fans the fun, and unique items they have been waiting for,” says <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/pranav-arora1/" target="_blank">Pranav Arora</a>, Head of Division.</p>
<p>Retailers and licensors new to the Just Funky name are likely familiar with their products. Fans of all ages and interests rely on Just Funky to provide their favorite novelty and collector’s items such as blankets, cups, buttons, and lanyards. From gaming and anime to music, movies and more, Just Funky provides brands and consumers with the go-to swag they need.</p>
<p>For gamers, Just Funky has licenses with Nintendo, PlayStation, and popular games including Pac-Man, Assassin’s Creed, Donkey Kong and The Legend of Zelda. Thanks to the talented team at Just Funky, gamers can curate their own collection of products and accessories, whether it’s figurines, flasks, or fleece.</p>
<p>Nowadays, television rivals the movie industry like never before. Those hooked on shows like Breaking Bad, The Walking Dead, and Doctor Who can thank Just Funky for their favorite household memorabilia. The company has manufactured goods such as a Breaking Bad Beaker Lamp and a Walking Dead Crossbow Coffee Mug.</p>
<p>Possibly one of the most influential industries when it comes to collectables and novelty items is the music industry. Just Funky has produced custom products for Bob Marley, Foo Fighters and Nirvana fanatics across the globe! The most recent addition to Just Funky’s music portfolio is international superstar Justin Bieber. In January 2017, Just Funky signed a licensing deal with Bravado to produce a collection of products for the iconic pop singer.</p>
<p>As Just Funky continues to spread into the EU marketplace, retailers and licensors have an opportunity to work with one of the fastest growing manufacturers in the game. Contact Just Funky today to find out how and where they can best serve you, and begin sharing your brand to a world of supporters.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://justfunky.com/blogs/news/just-funky-foundation-adds-sahil-arora-as-president</id>
    <published>2017-01-30T16:02:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2017-04-11T16:17:12-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://justfunky.com/blogs/news/just-funky-foundation-adds-sahil-arora-as-president"/>
    <title>Just Funky Foundation Adds Sahil Arora as President</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mike Gordon</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><strong class="date-line">Wooster, Ohio, January 30, 2017 (Newswire.com) - </strong><a href="http://www.justfunky.com/" target="_blank">The Just Funky Foundation</a> is pleased to announce that Sahil Arora has been appointed as the non-profit organization's President.</p>
<p>Through his new role, Sahil will continue to contribute to The Just Funky Foundation. He was previously the Co-Chairman and Vice President for The Just Funky Foundation, and played an enormous role in the astronomical growth of the non-profit.</p>
<p>Sahil also plays vital leadership roles in several companies, including: Just Funky, a private licensed and private merchandise manufacturer, as well as PSSR Holdings and Good Vibes Hospitality, owners of several quick-service franchises across Ohio. He also partakes in consulting both firms and consumers in the automotive and travel industries.</p>
<p>"Sahil’s brings a diverse set of skills and a long track record of successful leadership," said a source close to the appointment.</p>
<p>The Just Funky Foundation is passionate about creating opportunities for students and citizens everywhere by way of charitable giving. The non-profit was launched by Just Funky in January 2016 and continues to give back to the community.</p>
<p>Just Funky is a family-owned business with more than four decades of combined experience in manufacturing, licensing, retail, and creative development and offers manufacturing of licensed and private label merchandise. Through The Just Funky Foundation, the company can align with strategic partners to offer charitable contributions to students.</p>
<p>Most recently, Arora led a donation to the Wooster City School District. The donation included 5,000 lanyards, which was enough to provide one for each student and staff in the district grades K - 12. He also led a gift drive to benefit the Ronald McDonald House of Akron, collecting over 150 toys, toiletries, and other essentials to contribute to a happy Holiday season for the children and families at RMH. Sahil is currently working with leaders around the Wooster area to setup free tutoring in various subjects for the dedicated students of the Wooster City School District, who otherwise would not have access to this vital resource.</p>
<p>According to The Just Funky Foundation, "Sahil’s excellent leadership, along with his intense desire to better his community, will undoubtedly contribute to the growth of the Foundation and increase the impact and the number of those positively impacted by The Just Funky Foundation."</p>
<p><strong>About The Just Funky Foundation</strong></p>
<p>The Just Funky Foundation, a non-profit organization, is dedicated to delivering opportunities for students everywhere.</p>
<p>The Just Funky Foundation<br>Phone: 234-249-0145<br>E-mail: <a href="mailto:sahil@justfunky.com" target="_blank">p</a>r@justfunky.com<br>Website: www.justfunky.com</p>
<p>Source: Just Funky Foundation</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://justfunky.com/blogs/news/just-funky-signs-justin-bieber-licensing-deal</id>
    <published>2017-01-10T16:10:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2017-04-13T05:42:39-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://justfunky.com/blogs/news/just-funky-signs-justin-bieber-licensing-deal"/>
    <title>Just Funky Signs Justin Bieber Licensing Deal</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mike Gordon</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1881/5889/files/JF_LOGO_2b1a3d77-0bea-44cf-8a4e-b3a285055b6d_compact.png?v=1491941332" style="float: left;">
<p class="article-summary">Bravado signs a licensing deal with Just Funky to produce a collection of Justin Bieber products.</p>
<div class="marbot-15 html-content">
<p><strong class="date-line">Wooster, OH, January 10, 2017 (Newswire.com) - </strong><a href="http://www.justfunky.com/" target="_blank">​​​​​Just Funky</a>, a major producer of licensed and private label goods for the mainstream retail market, partners with <a href="http://www.bravado.com/" target="_blank">Bravado</a> to manufacture a <a href="http://www.justinbiebermusic.com/" target="_blank">Justin Bieber</a> collection of merchandise.</p>
<p>Under the agreement for the retail market in North America and Canada, <a href="http://www.justfunky.com/" target="_blank">Just Funky</a> will manufacture beverage-ware, fleece blankets, air fresheners, and many other accessories. </p>
<p><span>“The Just Funky team is thrilled to be working with the Bravado team and our valued retail partners to create a unique product for the Justin Bieber fan base,” says</span><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/pranav-arora1" target="_blank"> Pranav Arora</a><span>, Head of Division, Just Funky </span></p>
<p>Just Funky is a family-owned business that caters to over 20,000 independent stores in the United States, Canada, and the European Union. They also maintain partnerships with several prominent retailers in the nation, including big box retailers like Spencer’s, LootCrate, Target and Hot Topic.</p>
<p>With a primary goal of producing the most innovative product of the highest quality, Just Funky focuses on brainstorming novel and interesting ideas and translating them into actual merchandise for mainstream retail. They currently have over 110 employees and are headquartered in Wooster, Ohio. They also have offices located in Columbus, Ohio, Los Angeles, Hong Kong, and New Delhi. </p>
<p><strong>About Bravado</strong></p>
<p>Bravado, the only global, 360 degree full service merchandise company, develops and markets high-quality licensed merchandise to a world-wide audience. The company works closely with new and established entertainment clients, creating innovative products carefully tailored to each artist or brand. Product is sold on live tours, via selected retail outlets and through Web-based stores. Bravado also licenses rights to an extensive network of third-party licensees around the world. The company maintains offices in London, Los Angeles, New York, Berlin, Paris, Tokyo and Sydney. Now under the Universal Music Group umbrella, Bravado is able to leverage a global sales and distribution network from the world's largest record company, as well as the group's significant marketing strength. Bravado artists include The Rolling Stones, Lady Gaga, Michael Jackson, Justin Bieber, Paul McCartney, Eminem, Kanye West, Metallica, Nickelback, Katy Perry, Guns 'N Roses, Red Hot Chili Peppers, Green Day and The Killers, among many others.</p>
<p><strong>About Just Funky</strong></p>
<p>Just Funky is a premiere manufacturer of licensed and private label merchandise for the mainstream retail market. As a family owned business, our executives have combined over 44 years experience in manufacturing, licensing, retail and creative development in such areas as beverageware, impulse/novelty, decor, and apparel.</p>
<p>Just Funky’s main goal is to create the most innovative product with unmatched quality. We focus on brainstorming new ideas and being able to translate them to actual product for mainstream retail.</p>
<p><strong>Contact</strong></p>
<p>201 E. Liberty Street, Suite 202<br>Wooster, Ohio 44691<br>United States<br>234-249-0145<br><a href="mailto:pranav@justfunky.com" target="_blank">pranav@justfunky.com</a><br><a href="http://www.justfunky.com/" target="_blank">http://www.justfunky.com/</a></p>
<p>Source: Just Funky</p>
</div>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://justfunky.com/blogs/news/the-just-funky-foundation-names-pranav-arora-as-vice-president-and-chairman-of-the-board-of-directors</id>
    <published>2016-12-09T16:08:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2017-04-11T16:17:45-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://justfunky.com/blogs/news/the-just-funky-foundation-names-pranav-arora-as-vice-president-and-chairman-of-the-board-of-directors"/>
    <title>The Just Funky Foundation Names Pranav Arora as Vice President and Chairman of the Board of Directors</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mike Gordon</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1881/5889/files/JF_LOGO_2b1a3d77-0bea-44cf-8a4e-b3a285055b6d_compact.png?v=1491941332" style="float: left;"><br>
<p><strong class="date-line">Wooster, Ohio, December 9, 2016 (Newswire.com) - </strong>​The<a href="http://www.justfunky.com/" target="_blank"> Just Funky Foundation</a> is pleased to announce that they have named <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/prarora1" target="_blank">Pranav Arora</a> as the non-profit organization’s Vice President and Chairman of the Board of Directors.</p>
<p>Through his new role, Arora will continue to advocate for <a href="http://www.justfunky.com/" target="_blank">The Just Funky Foundation</a>. Arora was previously a board member for The Just Funky Foundation, and he was one of the key people in the astronomical growth of the non-profit.</p>
<p>Arora is also a board member of <a href="http://www.jmtdholdings.com/" target="_blank">JMTD Holdings</a>, an independent investment management firm. The firm is comprised of a powerful investor network, transaction intermediaries, and domain experts, and the company aims to unite entrepreneurial vision with experience.</p>
<p>“Pranav brings deep knowledge and a proven track record of being influential in media and business,” said a source close to the appointment.</p>
<p>The Just Funky Foundation is passionate about creating opportunities for students everywhere by way of charitable giving. The non-profit was launched by Just Funky in January 2016 and continues to give back to the community.</p>
<p>Just Funky is a family-owned business with more than four decades of combined experience in manufacturing, licensing, retail, and creative development and offers manufacturing of licensed and private label merchandise. Through The Just Funky Foundation, the company can align with strategic partners to offer charitable contributions to students.</p>
<p>Arora has already led The Just Funky Foundation in their mission.</p>
<p>Most recently, Arora led a donation to the Wooster City School District. The donation included 5,000 lanyards, which was enough to provide one for each student in the district grades K - 12.</p>
<p>According to The Just Funky Foundation, “I am confident Pranav’s unique experience will be very valuable as The Just Funky Foundation continues to grow and increases the masses we’ll positively affect.”</p>
<p><strong>About The Just Funky Foundation</strong></p>
<p>The Just Funky Foundation, a non-profit organization, is dedicated to delivering opportunities for students everywhere.</p>
<p><strong>Contact</strong></p>
<p>The Just Funky Foundation<br>Phone: 234-249-0145<br>E-mail: <a href="mailto:sahil@justfunky.com" target="_blank">sahil@justfunky.com</a><br>Website: justfunky.com</p>
<p>Source: Just Funky Foundation</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://justfunky.com/blogs/news/the-just-funky-foundation-announces-wooster-city-school-district-donation</id>
    <published>2016-11-15T16:18:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2017-04-11T16:21:07-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://justfunky.com/blogs/news/the-just-funky-foundation-announces-wooster-city-school-district-donation"/>
    <title>The Just Funky Foundation Announces Wooster City School District Donation</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mike Gordon</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1881/5889/files/JF_LOGO_2b1a3d77-0bea-44cf-8a4e-b3a285055b6d_compact.png?v=1491941332" style="float: left;"><br>
<p class="article-summary">5,000 custom lanyards were recently offered in a donation valued at $20,000</p>
<div class="marbot-15 html-content">
<p><strong class="date-line">Wooster, Ohio, November 15, 2016 (Newswire.com) - </strong>The <a href="http://www.justfunky.com/" target="_blank">Just Funky Foundation</a> has announced a donation to the Wooster City School District, which includes 5,000 lanyards valued at $20,000.</p>
<p>The <a href="http://www.justfunky.com/" target="_blank">Just Funky Foundation’s</a> co-chairman and executive vice president, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/prarora1" target="_blank">Pranav Arora</a> and Co-Chairman and President, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/sahil-arora-0168a773" target="_blank">Sahil Arora</a>, are the non-compensated creators of the non-profit organization, and both have strong ties with Wooster City. Both Pranav’s and Sahil’s alma mater is Wooster High School.</p>
<p>Just Funky, a premier manufacturer of licensed, labeled merchandise for retail, designed, developed, and manufactured the lanyards.</p>
<p>According to The Just Funky Foundation, their next goal is to continue working with the Wooster City School District to give back to the students. Through a direct partnership with the district’s superintendent, Dr. Tefs, Sahil and <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/prarora1" target="_blank">Pranav</a> plan to create more programs aligned to boost students.</p>
<p>In January 2016, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/prarora1" target="_blank">Pranav</a> and <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/sahil-arora-0168a773" target="_blank">Sahil</a> launched The Just Funky Foundation with a mission of giving back to the community, and the emphasis of their mission is education.</p>
<p>The Just Funky Foundation thanks the team at Just Funky, who worked tirelessly to spearhead all logistical elements of the lanyards. “All services and supplies, including the lanyards, were given to the Foundation at no charge by Just Funky,” according to The Just Funky Foundation.</p>
<p>Sahil worked directly with Dr. Tefs and the school’s principal, Tyler Keener, to propel the project, while Pranav worked diligently on an internal basis to ensure the project’s success. All students and staff received a custom lanyard designed for use with the school’s newly issues school I.D. cards, which were created to enhance the school’s security.</p>
<p>The Arora family is proud to partner with Wooster City Schools for this project, and they look forward to announcing exciting new projects soon.</p>
<p>The Just Funky Foundation<br>Phone: 234-249-0145<br>E-mail: <a href="mailto:Pranav@justfunky.com" target="_blank">Pranav@justfunky.com</a><br>Website: http://www.justfunky.com</p>
<p>Source: Just Funky</p>
</div>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://justfunky.com/blogs/news/4k-media-announces-licensing-agreement-with-just-funky</id>
    <published>2016-06-22T16:20:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2017-04-11T16:20:38-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://justfunky.com/blogs/news/4k-media-announces-licensing-agreement-with-just-funky"/>
    <title>4K Media Announces Licensing Agreement With Just Funky</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mike Gordon</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p class="article-summary">Just Funky is a premiere manufacturer of licensed and private label merchandise for the mainstream retail market. As a family owned business, Our executives have combined 44 years' experience in manufacturing, licensing, retail and creative development in such areas as beverageware, impulse/novelty, decor, and apparel. Just Funky's main goal is to create the most innovative product with unmatched quality. We focus on brainstorming new ideas and being able to translate them to</p>
<div class="marbot-15 html-content">
<p><strong class="date-line">Columbus Ohio, June 22, 2016 (Newswire.com) - </strong><span class="nanospell-typo">Shinichi</span> <span class="nanospell-typo">Hanamoto</span>, chairman and president of 4K Media Inc., a wholly-owned subsidiary of <span class="nanospell-typo">Konami</span> Digital Entertainment, Inc., announced today that a licensing deal has been finalized with <a href="http://justfunky.com/" target="_blank">Just Funky, LLC</a> to produce a collection of housewares, linens and accessories utilizing the Yu-Gi- Oh! artwork from its world record-setting trading card game. This artwork has only been available for licensing in North America since last spring.</p>
<p><span>Under the three year agreement for the North American market, </span><a href="https://justfunky.newswire.com/" target="_blank">Just Funky</a><span> will produce blankets and throws, cozies and ponchos, towels, wall art, pillows, shower curtains, lamps, glassware and other impulse items.</span></p>
<p><span>“We’re excited to partner with Just Funky to extend the Yu-Gi-Oh! brand to the home marketplace,” stated Jennifer Coleman, vice president of licensing and marketing at 4K Media Inc. “Our fans have a high level of engagement with the brand and these products will help deepen their loyalty and passion for Yu-Gi- Oh! in a fun and innovative way that was not available in the past.” </span></p>
<p><a href="http://justfunky.com/" target="_blank">Raj <span class="nanospell-typo">Arora</span></a>, CEO and president of Just Funky, said “This is a tremendous opportunity to work with one of the world’s most popular brands. We’re thrilled to be able to utilize the trading card artwork in a fashion that is sure to excite our consumers. We expect to see many of our multi-chain and independent specialty accounts support the brand as we develop unique and specialized items for Yu- Gi-Oh! fans across all ages.”</p>
<p><span class="nanospell-typo">￼The</span> Yu-Gi-Oh! series is currently in its 13th consecutive year of broadcast in the U.S. and most major markets worldwide. The series and brand continue to captivate children, particularly boys, through its best-selling trading card game, animated series and motion picture releases.</p>
<p>Source: Just Funky</p>
</div>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://justfunky.com/blogs/news/just-funky-signs-yu-gi-oh-licensee-deal</id>
    <published>2016-06-22T00:00:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2017-04-11T09:37:59-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://justfunky.com/blogs/news/just-funky-signs-yu-gi-oh-licensee-deal"/>
    <title>Just Funky Signs Yu-Gi-Oh! Licensee Deal</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mike Gordon</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<div class="marbot-15 html-content" style="float: left;">
<img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1881/5889/files/Yu-Gi-Oh.jpg?v=1490983800" style="float: left;">
<p class="article-summary">4K Media, a wholly owned subsidiary of Konami Digital Entertainment, has signed a licensing deal with Just Funky to produce a Yu-Gi-Oh! collection of housewares, linens and accessories.</p>
<p><strong class="date-line">Columbus, Ohio, June 22, 2016 (Newswire.com) - </strong>4K Media, a wholly owned subsidiary of <span class="nanospell-typo">Konami</span> Digital Entertainment, has signed a licensing deal with <a href="http://justfunky.com/" target="_blank">Just Funky</a> to produce a <a href="http://www.justfunky.com/#!yu-gj-oh/cq5o" target="_blank">Yu-Gi-Oh!</a> collection of housewares, linens and accessories.</p>
<p>Under the  agreement for the North American market, <a href="http://justfunky.com/" target="_blank">Just Funky</a>, a wholesaler that caters to all mass and more than 10,000 multi-chain and independent specialty stores worldwide, will produce blankets and throws, cozies and ponchos, towels, wall art, pillows, shower curtains, lamps, glassware and other impulse items.</p>
<p>The Yu-Gi-Oh! series is currently in its thirteenth consecutive year of broadcast in the US and in most major markets worldwide.</p>
<p>The series and brand continues in the form of trading card games, an animated series and DVD releases.</p>
<p>Source: Just Funky</p>
</div>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://justfunky.com/blogs/news/just-funky-confirms-licensing-agreement-for-one-punch-man</id>
    <published>2016-06-22T00:00:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2017-04-11T10:28:50-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://justfunky.com/blogs/news/just-funky-confirms-licensing-agreement-for-one-punch-man"/>
    <title>Just Funky Confirms Licensing Agreement for &quot;One-Punch Man.&quot;</title>
    <author>
      <name>Mike Gordon</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><strong class="date-line">Columbus Ohio, June 22, 2016 (Newswire.com) - </strong>The ONE-PUNCH MAN <span class="nanospell-typo">manga</span> series has become one of the most popular graphic novel titles in North America and is regularly on literary bestseller lists such as the New York Times and Nielsen <span class="nanospell-typo">BookScan</span>, while the <span class="nanospell-typo">anime</span> counterpart is watched by millions of fans <span class="nanospell-typo">online</span>.</p>
<p>VIZ Media will showcase ONE-PUNCH MAN among its extensive catalog of multimedia properties at the upcoming 2016 Licensing Expo in Las Vegas, NV. As the fan base for ONE-PUNCH MAN continues to expand across multiple key demographics throughout North America, the property will be well-supported by a diverse range of consumer products beginning later this year.</p>
<p><a href="http://justfunky.com/" target="_blank">Just Funky</a> has been added as a new product partner, focusing on Drink Wears and Accessories.</p>
<p><a href="http://justfunky.com/" target="_blank">Raj <span class="nanospell-typo">Arora</span></a>, CEO and president of Just Funky, said “This is a tremendous opportunity to work with one of the world’s most popular brands. We expect to see many of our multi-chain and independent specialty accounts support the brand as we develop unique and specialized items for "One Punch Man" fans across all ages.”</p>
<p><strong><a href="http://justfunky.com/" target="_blank">Just <span class="nanospell-typo">Funky’s</span></a> </strong>main goal is to create the most innovative product with unmatched quality. We focus on brainstorming new ideas and being able to translate them to actual product for mainstream retail.</p>
<p><strong><a href="http://justfunky.com/" target="_blank">Just Funky</a></strong> is a premiere manufacturer of licensed and private label merchandise for the mainstream retail market. As a family owned business, Our executives have combined 44 years' experience in manufacturing, licensing, retail and creative development in such areas as <span class="nanospell-typo">beverageware</span>, impulse/novelty, decor, and apparel.</p>
<p>Source: Just Funky</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
